<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>HTML/CSS on Tortugas Consulting, LLC</title>
    <link>https://tortugas-llc.com/technologies/html/css/</link>
    <description>Recent content in HTML/CSS on Tortugas Consulting, LLC</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <managingEditor>projects@tortugas-llc.com (Matthew M. Keeler)</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>projects@tortugas-llc.com (Matthew M. Keeler)</webMaster>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 17:12:33 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://tortugas-llc.com/technologies/html/css/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Kansas Life</title>
      <link>https://tortugas-llc.com/kansas-life/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Jan 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>projects@tortugas-llc.com (Matthew M. Keeler)</author>
      <guid>https://tortugas-llc.com/kansas-life/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Kansas Life is an independent insurance agency.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Kansas Life is one of our oldest and most trusted clients. For years, Tortugas has partnered with them to develop an in-house payroll and policy tracking system to help automate their workload and reduce operating costs.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Panna</title>
      <link>https://tortugas-llc.com/panna/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>projects@tortugas-llc.com (Matthew M. Keeler)</author>
      <guid>https://tortugas-llc.com/panna/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Panna is an innovative cooking platform that brings professional culinary instruction to home cooks through engaging video content.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We partnered with Panna to build key features of their web platform, combining PHP backend services with a modern React frontend. Our work helped create an interactive and engaging experience for users learning to cook from world-class chefs.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Natural Organic Warehouse</title>
      <link>https://tortugas-llc.com/natural-organic-warehouse/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Sep 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>projects@tortugas-llc.com (Matthew M. Keeler)</author>
      <guid>https://tortugas-llc.com/natural-organic-warehouse/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Natural Organic Warehouse is a leading distributor of natural and organic food products.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We partnered with Natural Organic Warehouse to develop a comprehensive website and backend database system. The custom application streamlines their operations, manages inventory, and provides their team with powerful tools to serve their customers more effectively.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Startup Wichita</title>
      <link>https://tortugas-llc.com/startup-wichita/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jan 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>projects@tortugas-llc.com (Matthew M. Keeler)</author>
      <guid>https://tortugas-llc.com/startup-wichita/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Startup Wichita is a community organization dedicated to fostering entrepreneurship and innovation in Wichita, Kansas.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We built a modern web platform using Node.js to help connect entrepreneurs, provide resources, and showcase the vibrant startup ecosystem in Wichita. The platform serves as a central hub for the local startup community.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Young Life Global Leaders</title>
      <link>https://tortugas-llc.com/young-life-leaders/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jan 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>projects@tortugas-llc.com (Matthew M. Keeler)</author>
      <guid>https://tortugas-llc.com/young-life-leaders/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Young Life Developing Global Leaders is a non-profit organization focused on training and developing leaders around the world.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We developed a custom Ruby on Rails application for Young Life Global Leaders to manage their programs, track participants, and provide resources for leaders worldwide. The platform has been instrumental in helping them scale their impact globally.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Young Life Wichita</title>
      <link>https://tortugas-llc.com/young-life-wichita/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Jan 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>projects@tortugas-llc.com (Matthew M. Keeler)</author>
      <guid>https://tortugas-llc.com/young-life-wichita/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Young Life Wichita is a local chapter of Young Life, a Christian youth ministry organization.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We created a dynamic website for Young Life Wichita using Ruby on Rails to help them connect with students, share updates, and manage their events and programs. The site serves as a vital communication tool for their ministry in the Wichita area.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
